Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
The weather is nice today.
Yes, it's very good weather.
What will you do today?
From the afternoon
With friends
Watch a movie.
That sounds nice.
What movie is it?
It's an action movie.
Me too, action.
I like movies.
That's something to look forward to.
But first, let's have lunch.
Let's eat.
Yes, that's a good idea.
What would you like to eat?
I want to eat sushi.
That's nice.
I also like sushi.
Do you have any recommended shops?
Do you have it?
Yes,
That place is very
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Let's go there.
Let's go!
I hope the road isn't crowded.
Yes, I agree. I don't like traffic jams.
Shall we go by train?
Yes, that might be faster.
The station is this way.
I'll buy the tickets.
Thank you, I'll wait.
I've bought the tickets.
Thank you. Let's go.
The train will arrive in 5 minutes.
That's just right.
Oh, the train has arrived!
Let's get on.
There are empty seats.
Lucky us!
Where do we get off next?
It's the third station.
Got it.
What a beautiful view.
Indeed. Spring is beautiful.
Oh, let's get off!
Yes, do you have everything?
I'm fine.
Is the store nearby?
Yes, it's a 5-minute walk.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's here!
Wow, what a beautiful store.
Let's go inside.
Welcome!
Hello, two people.
Please this way.
Thank you.
Here's the menu.
Thank you. It's hard to decide.
Everything looks delicious.
I'll have the tuna.
Then, I'll have the salmon.
May I order?
Yes, go ahead.
One tuna and one salmon, please.
Certainly.
It's exciting!
I'm hungry.
Oh, they've arrived!
Looks delicious!
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's very tasty!
That's great.
After we finish eating, it's the movies.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Where is the venue?
It's near the station.
Then, we'll take the train again.
That's right. Let's walk after eating.
It will be good exercise.
I'm already full.
Shall we go now?
Could I have the bill, please?
Thank you very much!
Thanks for the meal!
The movie theater is this way.
We're almost there.
Oh, there are a lot of people.
It's a popular movie, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it!
Have you reserved the seats?
Yes, everything is set!
Let's go in!