Good morning.
How are you?
Yes, I'm doing well.
The weather is nice today, isn't it?
Yes, it's very nice weather.
What are you doing today?
In the afternoon,
I'm going to watch a movie
with my friends.
That sounds great.
What movie is it?
It's an action movie.
I also like action movies.
That sounds exciting.
But let's have lunch first.
Yes, that's a good idea.
What would you like to eat for lunch?
Sushi sounds good to me.
Yes, let's go for sushi then.
What type of sushi do you like?
That's great.
I also love sushi.
Do you have any recommended places to go?
Yes, there is one place that is very delicious.
It's there.
Thank you,
Let's go there then.
Thank you very much.
Then let's go there.
Let's go!