Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
The weather is nice today.
Yes, it's very good weather.
What will you do today?
From the afternoon
With friends
Watch a movie.
That sounds nice.
What movie is it?
It's an action movie.
Me too, action.
I like movies.
That's something to look forward to.
But first, let's have lunch.
Let's eat.
Yes, that's a good idea.
What would you like to eat?
I want to eat sushi.
That's nice.
I also like sushi.
Do you have any recommended shops?
Do you have it?
Yes,
That place is very
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Let's go there.
Let's go!
I hope the road isn't crowded.
Yes, I agree. I don't like traffic jams.
Shall we go by train?
Yes, that might be faster.
The station is this way.
I'll buy the tickets.
Thank you, I'll wait.
I've bought the tickets.
Thank you. Let's go.
The train will arrive in 5 minutes.
That's just right.
Oh, the train has arrived!
Let's get on.
There are empty seats.
Lucky us!
Where do we get off next?
It's the third station.
Got it.
What a beautiful view.
Indeed. Spring is beautiful.
Oh, let's get off!
Yes, do you have everything?
I'm fine.
Is the store nearby?
Yes, it's a 5-minute walk.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's here!
Wow, what a beautiful store.
Let's go inside.
Welcome!
Hello, two people.
Please this way.
Thank you.
Here's the menu.
Thank you. It's hard to decide.
Everything looks delicious.
I'll have the tuna.
Then, I'll have the salmon.
May I place an order?
Yes, go ahead.
One tuna and one salmon, please.
Certainly.
It's exciting!
I'm hungry.
Oh, they've arrived!
Looks delicious!
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's very tasty!
That's good to hear.
After eating, it's the movie.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Where is the venue?
It's near the station.
Then, we'll take the train again.
That's right. Let's walk after eating.
It will be good exercise.
I'm already full.
Shall we go now?
Could I have the bill, please?
Thank you very much!
Thanks for the meal!
The movie theater is this way.
We're almost there.
Oh, there are a lot of people.
It's a popular movie, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it!
Do you have a reservation for the seats?
Yes, it's all set!
Let's go in!
Nice seats.
Not too close, not too far back.
The movie is about to start.
Do you have popcorn?
Of course, I bought some.
Thank you!
Let's be quiet now.
Yes, it's starting!
Wow, it's so powerful.
The sound is amazing!
Be quiet, other customers...
Sorry.
It's okay, let's enjoy it.
This scene is amazing!
I'm really on the edge of my seat.
Oh, it's over!
That was fantastic!
It's been a while since I enjoyed something this much.
Let's watch a movie together again.
Absolutely!
Well, shall we head home soon?
Yes, I think so.
It's already dark outside.
The night breeze feels nice.
Indeed it does.
I had a great day today.
I think so too.
Let's go out again next time.
Of course!
Where shall we go next?
How about an amusement park?
Sounds good! The thrill rides!
It's a bit scary, but it looks fun!
Then, let's make a plan.
Are you free next Saturday?
Yes, I'm available!
Alright, it's settled then.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too!
We're arriving at the station soon.
Well then, it's time to say goodbye here.
Thank you for today!
You're welcome, I had a great time.
Please be careful on your way home.
Yes, good night.
Good night.
I'll contact you again.
I'm waiting!
Bye-bye!
(Sound of train)
Today was a good day again.
I hope another fun day will come.
(Music)
What should I do when I get home?
Take a shower...
And then, I'll play some games.
I bought a new game.
That sounds interesting.
Let's play together next time.
Absolutely!
Well, I've arrived home.
I'm home~
Welcome back!
Was it a good day?
Yes, it was really great.
That's good to hear.
I'm a bit tired though.
Take a good rest.
Thank you.
Well, I'm going to take a shower.
Okay.
(Sound of shower)
Phew, I feel refreshed!
Now, it's game time!
Power on!
(Game startup sound)
I'm so excited!
(Game play begins)
Wow, it's hard from the start!
Good luck!
Thank you!
...Oh, I got defeated!
Don't worry!
Let's retry!
This time for sure!
Go!
I cleared it!
Amazing!
Today was a good day.
Delicious food, fun movies,
and games!
It's time to sleep now.
Good night.
Hope tomorrow will be a good day too.
(Soft music)
Zzz...
(Night insects' sounds)
Good night.
(Fade out)
(Morning birds chirping)
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I slept soundly.
It's a beautiful weather today.
Indeed. Such a refreshing morning.
What shall we have for breakfast?
I want to eat pancakes.
Then shall we make them together?
Yes!
Do we have the ingredients?
Yes, everything is ready.
Then, let's get the eggs and milk...
The flour is here.
Leave the mixing to me!
Wow, you're good at this.
I'll heat up the frying pan.
It smells so good!
They're done!
Let's eat!
Yum, it's delicious!
The sweetness is just right.
Happy from the morning~
What are today's plans?
Cleaning and shopping.
I'll help too!
Thank you, that helps!
First, the vacuum cleaner.
Yes, turn it on!
(Vacuum cleaner sound)
Shall we wipe the windows too?
Sounds good, let's make them sparkling.
Finished!
Good job!
Shall we go shopping now?
Let's go!
Do you have the shopping list?
Yes, I wrote it on a note.
Then, no forgetfulness!
Yep, perfect!
The supermarket is just ahead.
It's quite crowded.
Maybe because it's a holiday.
I'll get the cart.
Thank you!
Let's start with the vegetables.
Tomatoes and lettuce.
And carrots too.
Got it!
Next is the meat section.
Let's buy chicken and pork.
Ingredients for dinner.
What shall we make today?
Maybe chicken teriyaki.
Sounds delicious!
Please tell me the recipe later.
Of course!
Shall we check out?
The register is over there.
Let's line up.
The line is quite long...
But it seems to be moving quickly.
Okay, payment complete!
Thank you~
Let's head home!
The bags are quite heavy.
Let's carry them carefully!
It's good exercise.
Let's rest a bit when we get home.
Yes, let's do that.
We're home!
I'm back~
I'll put away the groceries.
Thank you!
Would you like some tea?
Sounds good, a little break.
I'll make some tea.
Thank you. Today has been fulfilling.
Really, it's such a nice day.
I wish days like this would last forever.
Yes, I agree.
Now, let's start preparing dinner.
I'll help!
Please cut the vegetables.
Got it!
The rice is already cooked.
Everything's ready!
All that's left is to cook the chicken.
Sizzle...
It smells so good!
Pour the teriyaki sauce.
It's done!
Let's eat!
Wow, it's the best!
Thank you for today.
Likewise, I had fun.
Let's continue to do this.
I want to be with you forever.
Me too, forever.
(Fade out with gentle music)
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
Yes, it's especially good when we make it ourselves.
Shall we clean up too?
Yes, let's do it together.
I'll carry the dishes.
Thank you, I'll wash them.
The sponge is here.
That helps a lot!
It's clean now.
Cleaning up feels so refreshing.
Well then, shall we relax a bit?
Yes, relaxing on the sofa.
Shall we watch TV?
Sounds good. I wonder what's on?
Here's the remote.
Thank you.
The drama has started.
I like this actor.
Their acting is natural and good.
The story is interesting too.
I look forward to it every week.
Let's watch it again next week!
Of course!
Oh, it's bath time.
Yes, it is. Who goes first?
You go ahead.
Thank you. I'll go now.
(Sound of bath)
Phew, that was a nice bath!
I'm going in next.
Take care!
(Relaxing music)
Today went by so quickly.
I wish every day was like this.
(Coming back from the bath)
I feel refreshed~
I've changed into pajamas!
Let's go to bed soon.
Yes, I think so.
We have an early day tomorrow.
I'll brush my teeth.
I'll do it later.
(Sound of brushing teeth)
Good night first.
Good night.
Sweet dreams.
You too.
(Quiet night sounds)
See you tomorrow.
Zzz...
(Morning after night)
A new morning has come.
The alarm is ringing.
Good morning~
I'm still sleepy…
But I have to get up.
Let's do our best today!
What shall we have for breakfast?
Just toast and coffee, simple.
Okay, I'll prepare it!
Thank you!
The aroma of coffee is the best.
I'm waking up now.
What's today's plan?
Work in the morning, free in the afternoon.
Let's meet again in the afternoon!
Yes, looking forward to it!
See you!
I'm off!
(Sound of the front door)
Let's do our best today!
(Sound of commuting)
Caught the train just in time.
Lucky to get a seat!
Hope today's work goes well.
Arrived~
Good morning!
Thanks for your help today.
Likewise!
(At work)
Where was this document?
It was attached to the email.
Oh, thank you!
No problem~
It's progressing smoothly.
Almost done.
Let's do our best!
Yes!
It's lunchtime~
What shall we eat?
Let's go to a nearby cafe!
Sounds good!
(Cafe sounds)
I'll order pasta.
I'll have a sandwich.
That looks delicious!
I think I can do well in the afternoon.
Me too!
Let's go back now.
Yeah, let's stay focused in the afternoon too!
(Office sounds)
It's already evening in no time.
Good job today!
See you tomorrow~
Well then, let's go home.
The train is coming.
Just in time!
I wonder what I'll do when I get home.
Maybe have dinner and relax.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Thanks for your hard work today.
Thank you. What should we have for dinner?
There's leftover curry in the fridge!
Great!
I'll warm it up.
Let's eat!
It's delicious again today~
I'm happy.
Really.
(Soft background music)
Let's do our best together again tomorrow.
Yeah!
I'm starting to feel sleepy.
Then, it's time to get ready for bed.
Brush your teeth, change into pajamas...
Get into bed...
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
Zzz...
(Quiet night)
(Sound of stars shining)
The end credits roll.
Thank you for today as well.
May another wonderful day begin.
(Background music fades out)
To be continued...
Special thanks to you.
Good night.
🌙
(Morning sun shining in)
Good morning, it's a new day again.
Let's start together today.
Shall we do a little stretch?
Yes, it makes my body feel refreshed.
(Sound of stretching)
Alright, morning preparations!
I'm going to take a shower.
See you later.
(Sound of shower)
Phew, I feel refreshed!
What shall we have for breakfast?
Today, toast and fried eggs.
Yes, I'll prepare it!
I'll also make some coffee.
That would be helpful~
Let's eat!
Yes, a good start to the day!
Thank you for the meal!
Well, let's get ready to go out.
What was today's schedule again?
Shopping in the morning, a walk in the afternoon!
Sounds nice, a relaxing day.
The weather looks good too.
Alright, let's prepare and head out.
Wallet, smartphone, keys, got it!
I'm off!
Take care!
(Lively outdoor sounds)
The city is lively again today.
Many people are walking around.
It seems this cafe just opened.
Shall we stop by later?
Sounds good!
First, let's go to the supermarket.
Let's look at the list and shop.
Vegetables, milk, bread...
And some sweets too.
And maybe some ice cream as well!
Sounds good!
Let's line up at the register.
It looks like it will be quick.
Payment is complete!
Thank you very much!
Now, to that new cafe!
The menu looks stylish.
Maybe I'll try the matcha latte.
I'll have a caramel macchiato!
I'll place the order.
The staff is also very kind.
It's a nice atmosphere in this shop.
I want to come here again.
Really!
I'll enjoy this delicious drink!
It's so relaxing.
Well then, shall we go for an afternoon walk?
Let's go to the park!
The spring breeze feels so good.
Let's chat while walking.