Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
The weather is nice today.
Yes, it's very good weather.
What will you do today?
From the afternoon
With friends
We will watch a movie.
That sounds nice.
What kind of movie is it?
It's an action movie.
Me too, action.
I like movies.
That sounds fun.
But, first, lunch.
Let's eat.
Yes, that's a good idea.
What would you like to eat?
I want to eat sushi.
That's nice.
I also like sushi.
Do you have any recommended shops?
Do you have it?
Yes,
That place over there is very...
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Let's go there.
Let's go!
I hope the road isn't crowded.
Yes, I agree. I don't like traffic jams.
Shall we go by train?
Yes, that might be faster.
The station is this way.
I'll buy the tickets.
Thank you, I'll wait.
I've bought the tickets.
Thank you. Let's go.
The train will arrive in 5 minutes.
That's just right.
Oh, the train has arrived!
Let's get on.
There are empty seats.
Lucky us!
Where do we get off next?
It's the third station.
Got it.
What a beautiful view.
Indeed. Spring is beautiful.
Oh, let's get off!
Yes, do you have everything?
I'm fine.
Is the store nearby?
Yes, it's a 5-minute walk.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's here!
Wow, what a beautiful store.
Let's go inside.
Welcome!
Hello, two people.
Please this way.
Thank you.
Here's the menu.
Thank you. It's hard to decide.
Everything looks delicious.
I'll have the tuna.
Then, I'll have the salmon.
May I place an order?
Yes, go ahead.
One tuna and one salmon, please.
Certainly.
It's exciting!
I'm hungry.
Oh, they've arrived!
Looks delicious!
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's very tasty!
That's good to hear.
After we finish eating, it's the movies.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Where is the venue?
It's near the station.
Then, we'll take the train again.
That's right. Let's walk after eating.
It will be good exercise.
I'm already full.
Shall we go now?
Could I have the bill, please?
Thank you very much!
Thanks for the meal!
The movie theater is this way.
We're almost there.
Oh, there are a lot of people.
It's a popular movie, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it!
Have you reserved the seats?
Yes, perfectly!
Let's go in!
Nice seats.
Not too close, not too far back.
The movie is about to start.
Do you have popcorn?
Of course, I bought some.
Thank you!
Let's be quiet now.
Yes, it's starting!
Wow, it's so powerful.
The sound is amazing too!
Be quiet, other customers...
Sorry.
It's okay, let's enjoy it.
This scene is amazing!
I'm really on the edge of my seat.
Ah, it's over!
That was fantastic!
It's been a while since I enjoyed something this much.
Let's watch a movie together again.
Absolutely!
Well, shall we head home soon?
Yes, I think so.
It's already dark outside.
The night breeze feels nice.
Indeed, it does.
I had a great day today.
I think so too.
Let's go out again next time.
Of course!
Where shall we go next?
How about an amusement park?
Sounds good! The thrill rides!
It's a bit scary, but it looks fun!
Then, let's make a plan.
Are you free next Saturday?
Yes, I am!
Then it's settled.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too!
We're arriving at the station soon.
Well then, it's time to say goodbye here.
Thank you for today!
You're welcome, I had a great time.
Please be careful on your way home.
Yes, good night.
Good night.
I'll contact you again.
I'll be waiting!
Bye-bye!
(Sound of train)
Today was a good day again.
I hope another fun day will come.
(Music)
I wonder what I'll do when I get home.
Take a shower...
And then, I'll play some games.
I bought a new game.
That sounds interesting.
Let's play together next time.
Absolutely!
Well, I've arrived home.
I'm home~
Welcome back!
Was it a good day?
Yes, it was really great.
That's good to hear.
I'm a bit tired though.
Take a good rest.
Thank you.
Well, I'm going to take a shower.
Okay.
(Sound of shower)
Phew, I feel refreshed!
Now, it's game time!
Power on!
(Game startup sound)
I'm so excited!
(Game play begins)
Wow, it's hard from the start!
Good luck!
Thank you!
...Oh, I got defeated!
Don't worry!
Let's retry!
This time for sure!
Go!
I cleared it!
Amazing!
Today was a good day.
Delicious food, fun movies,
and games!
It's time to sleep now.
Good night.
Hope tomorrow will be a good day too.
(Soft music)
Zzz...
(Night insects' sounds)
Good night.
(Fade out)
(Morning birds chirping)
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I slept soundly.
It's a beautiful weather today.
Indeed. Such a refreshing morning.
What shall we have for breakfast?
I want to eat pancakes.
Then shall we make them together?
Yes!
Do we have the ingredients?
Yes, everything is ready.
Then, let's get the eggs and milk...
The flour is here.
Leave the mixing to me!
Wow, you're good at this.
I'll heat up the frying pan.
I can smell something delicious!
They're done!
Let's eat!
Mmm, it's delicious!
The sweetness is just right.
Happy from the morning~
What are today's plans?
Cleaning and shopping.
Then I'll help too!
Thank you, that helps!
First, let's start with the vacuum cleaner.
Yes, turn it on!
(Sound of vacuum)
Shall we also wipe the windows?
Sounds good, let's make them sparkling.
Finished!
Good job!
Shall we go shopping now?
Let's go!
Do you have the shopping list?
Yes, I wrote it on a note.
Then we won't forget anything.
Yes, perfect!
The supermarket is just ahead.
It's quite crowded.
Maybe because it's a holiday.
I'll get the cart.
Thank you!
Let's start with the vegetables.
Tomatoes and lettuce.
And carrots too.
Got it!
Next is the meat section.
Let's buy chicken and pork.
Ingredients for dinner.
What shall we make today?
Maybe chicken teriyaki.
Sounds delicious!
Please tell me the recipe later.
Of course!
Shall we check out?
The register is over there.
Let's line up.
The line is quite long...
But it seems to be moving quickly.
Okay, payment completed!
Thank you~
Let's head home!
The bags are quite heavy.
Let's carry them carefully!
It's good exercise.
Let's rest a bit when we get home.
Yes, let's do that.
We're back!
I'm home~
I'll put away the groceries.
Thank you!
Would you like some tea?
Sounds good, a little break.
I'll make some tea.
Thank you. Today has been fulfilling.
Really, it's such a nice day.
I wish days like this would last forever.
Yes, I agree.
Now, let's start preparing dinner.
I'll help!
Please cut the vegetables.
Got it!
The rice is already cooked.
Everything's ready!
All that's left is to cook the chicken.
Sizzle...
That smells so good!
I'll pour the teriyaki sauce.
It's done!
Let's eat!
Wow, it's the best!
Thank you for today.
Likewise, I had fun.
Let's keep doing this.
I want to be with you forever.
Me too, forever.
(Fade out with gentle music)
Thank you for the meal.
That was delicious.
Yes, it's especially good when we make it ourselves.
Shall I clean up too?
Yes, let's do it together.
I'll carry the dishes.
Thank you, I'll wash them.
The sponge is here.
That helps a lot!
It's clean now.
Cleaning up feels so refreshing.
Then, shall we relax a bit?
Yes, relaxing on the sofa.
Shall we watch TV?
Sounds good. I wonder what's on?
Here's the remote.
Thank you.
The drama has started.
I like this actor.
Their acting is so natural, it's great.
The story is interesting too.
I look forward to it every week.
Let's watch it again next week!
Of course!
Oh, it's bath time.
Yes, it is. Who goes first?
You go ahead.
Thank you. I'll go now.
(Sound of bath water)
Phew, that was a nice bath!
I'm going in next.
Have a good bath!
(Relaxing music)
Today went by so quickly.
I wish every day was like this.
(Coming back from the bath)
Feeling refreshed!
I've changed into my pajamas!
Let's go to bed soon.
Yes, that's a good idea.
We have an early day tomorrow.
I'll brush my teeth.
I'll do it later.
(Sound of brushing teeth)
Good night first.
Good night.
Sweet dreams.
You too.
(Quiet night sounds)
See you tomorrow.
Zzz...
(Morning breaks)
A new morning has come.
The alarm is ringing.
Good morning!
I'm still sleepy...
But I have to get up.
Let's do our best today!
What should we have for breakfast?
Just toast and coffee, simple.
Okay, I'll prepare it!
Thank you!
The smell of coffee is wonderful.
I'm waking up now.
What's today's plan?
Work in the morning, free in the afternoon.
Let's meet again in the afternoon!
Yes, I'm looking forward to it!
See you!
I'm off!
(Sound of the front door)
Let's do our best today!
(Sound of commuting)
Caught the train just in time.
Lucky to get a seat!
Hope everything goes well at work today.
Arrived!
Good morning!
Thanks for your help today.
Likewise!
(At work)
Where was this document?
It was attached to the email.
Thank you!
No problem!
Progress is going smoothly.
Almost done.
Let's keep it up!
Yes!
It's lunchtime!
What shall we eat?
Let's go to a nearby cafe!
Sounds good!
(Cafe sounds)
I'll have pasta.
I'll have a sandwich.
Looks delicious!
I think I can manage the afternoon.
Me too!
Let's head back now.
Yes, let's stay focused in the afternoon too!
(Office sounds)
It's already evening in no time.
Good job today!
See you tomorrow~
Well then, let's go home.
The train is coming, isn't it?
Just in time!
I wonder what I should do when I get home.
Maybe have dinner and relax.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Thanks for your hard work today.
Thank you. What should we have for dinner?
There's leftover curry in the fridge!
Awesome!
I'll warm it up.
Let's eat!
It's delicious today too~
I'm happy.
Me too.
(Calm background music)
Let's do our best together again tomorrow.
Yeah!
I'm starting to feel sleepy soon.
Then, it's time to get ready for bed.
Brush my teeth, change into pajamas...
Get into bed...
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
Zzz...
(Night quietness)
(Sound of stars shining)
The end roll plays.
Thank you for today.
Hope a wonderful day begins again.
(Music fades out)
To be continued...
Special thanks to you.
Good night.
🌙
(Morning sun shines in)
Good morning, a new day begins.
Let's start again today.
Shall we do some stretching?
Yes, it makes the body feel refreshed.
(Stretching sounds)
Alright, morning preparations!
I'll take a shower.
Have a good day.
(Shower sounds)
Phew, feeling refreshed!
What shall we have for breakfast?
Today, toast and fried eggs.
Okay, I'll prepare!
I'll also make coffee.
Thanks!
Let's eat!
Yes, a good start today too!
Thank you for the meal!
Now, let's get ready to go out.
What was today's plan?
Shopping in the morning, walk in the afternoon!
Sounds good, a relaxing day.
The weather looks nice too.
Then, let's prepare and head out.
Wallet, smartphone, keys, all set!
I'm off!
Take care!
(Lively outdoor sounds)
The city is lively today too.
Many people are walking around.
It seems this cafe just opened.
Shall we drop by later?
Sounds good!
First, to the supermarket.
Let's buy while looking at the list.
Vegetables, milk, bread...
And some snacks too.
And ice cream!
Nice~
Let's line up at the register.
It'll be quick.
Payment completed!
Thank you very much~
Now, to that new cafe!
The menu looks stylish.
Maybe I'll try a matcha latte.
I'll have a caramel macchiato!
I'll order now.
The staff is also friendly.
It's a nice atmosphere here.
I want to come again.
Really!
Enjoying a delicious drink!
It's relaxing~
Now, let's go for an afternoon walk.
Let's go to the park!
The spring breeze feels good.
Let's walk and chat.
Let's sit on the bench and rest for a bit.
Nice, this view is also wonderful.
The leaves of the trees are swaying in the wind.
It feels like time is flowing slowly.
The birds' chirping is also pleasant, isn't it?
Oh, there's a squirrel over there!
Really! So cute!
Time like this is very healing.
Doing nothing is a luxury, isn't it?
The sunset is gradually tilting.
Shall we head home soon?
Yes, let's walk home slowly.
The way back is also quiet and nice.
We walked a lot today.
It was good exercise!
What shall we have for dinner?
I want something light.
Then let's have cold Chinese noodles!
Great idea!
I think we have the ingredients.
Let's make it after we get home.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Let's prepare the cold Chinese noodles right away.
Cut the vegetables, boil the noodles...
Shall we make the sauce ourselves?
Yes, homemade tastes much better!
It's ready!
Let's eat!
Mmm, it tastes like summer!
It's refreshing and delicious.
It blows away the fatigue.
Thank you for the meal!
Let's take a bath now...
How about watching a movie today?
Sounds good! What do you want to watch?
Something heartwarming would be nice.
How about this animated movie?
Oh, that's one I've wanted to see for a while!
Okay, I'll play it.
(Playing sound)
The visuals are beautiful!
The music is wonderful.
I'm drawn into this world.
That character is so cute!
The character is also very nice.
I heard there are tear-jerking scenes in the second half.
Better prepare a handkerchief!
(Emotional music)
I cried.
Me too... it was a good movie.
After watching, my heart feels warm.
I want to watch this again.
Yes, it's a precious film.
Let's go to bed soon.
Yes, today was a day full of activity.
Brush my teeth, change into pajamas...
Hope tomorrow will be another good day.
Good night.
Good night~
Zzz...
(Night insects chirping)
(Moon visible from the window)
The quiet night passes by...
...
(Morning birds chirping)
Good morning.
Did you sleep well yesterday?
Yes, I slept soundly!
It's a bit cool today.
I can feel the signs of autumn.
What shall we have for breakfast?
Let's have miso soup and rice.
A Japanese-style breakfast sounds good!
Then, let's dissolve the miso...
Add tofu and wakame seaweed.
Smells so good~
Well then, let's eat!
It has a soothing taste.
It's comforting from the morning.
Thank you for the meal!
So, how will you spend today?
I feel like going to the library.
That sounds nice, a relaxing time reading books.
Let's look for a favorite novel.
Let's go out once we're ready!
Yes, I'm leaving!
Take care!
(Quietness of the library)
It has a calm atmosphere.
I'm interested in that shelf.
Yeah, that book... looks interesting!
Let's read a little.
The sound of flipping pages is pleasant.
I lose track of time reading.
It's about time to go home.
Let's borrow this book.
Looking forward to reading more.
(On the way back)
Would you like to stop by somewhere?
There's a dango shop.
We've been tempted by sweets~
Let's get mitarashi dango and anko dango!
I love both!
Let's enjoy!
The sweet and salty flavor is irresistible.
I also want some Japanese tea.
Oh, there might be a tea shop nearby!
Let's stop by for a bit!
Hello~
Welcome!
May I have some sencha?
Yes, I'll bring it right away.
The aroma is really wonderful.
One sip and I feel so relaxed.
Indeed, a Japanese-style time is nice.
It's about time for full autumn now.
I want to go see the autumn leaves.
Yeah, maybe next week!
Let's make some plans.
Another thing to look forward to!
The way home is filled with smiles.
Let's rest a little when we get home.
We walked a lot today!
Then, let's continue reading the book while drinking tea.
It's the best afternoon.
A quiet time flows luxuriously...
Let's spend a little more time reading like this.
This novel is interesting because the plot is unpredictable.
The characters are also charming.
I can't help but keep turning the pages.
Oh, it's already this late!
I should start preparing dinner soon.
What should we have today?
How about stew?
It's the season when we want to eat something warm.
I wonder if I have all the ingredients... Yes, I have everything!
Well then, let's start cooking.
Cutting vegetables and simmering them slowly.
The gentle bubbling sound is so soothing.
The whole room is filled with the aroma of stew.
Is it almost ready?
Yes, it looks delicious!
Let's eat.
Wow, it melts in your mouth!
It's hot and warms my heart.
Dipping bread into it makes it even more special.
Ah, happiness~
Do we have any dessert?
There should be pudding in the refrigerator!
Great! Let's eat later!
Would you like to listen to some music after the meal?
Yeah, I feel like listening to some relaxing jazz.
(Jazz piano music plays)
This song is nice.
Sitting on the sofa with my eyes closed...
Losing myself in the sound.
It's truly a luxurious time.
I might doze off a little.
But it's still too early to sleep.
That's right, I think I'll organize my albums.
There are many nostalgic photos.
This one is from elementary school field trip!
Haha, making a funny face~
This photo is from the school festival, isn't it?
It brings back memories of youth.
Each photo has its own story.
I should organize this album more.
Maybe I should digitize them.
I'll try scanning them next time.
Records I want to leave for the future.
Well, it's about time for dessert!
I'll have the pudding~!
The sweetness is just right, it's the best.
I can't stop eating with my spoon.
Maybe I should try making this myself?
Nice, homemade pudding!
Let's try making it on the next holiday.
What kind of mold should I use?
A heart shape, or maybe a star shape!
Our joys have increased again.
Today was a very peaceful day.
The night quietly deepens.
At the end of the day, I feel grateful.
I hope tomorrow will be another good day.
It's about time to sleep, isn't it?
Change into pajamas, brush your teeth...
Get into bed and take a deep breath.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
(The quiet of the night continues)
Zzz...
(Morning light through the curtains)
Good morning.
It's sunny again today!
I feel refreshed upon waking.
Let's go to the balcony to breathe in the morning air.
The breeze is pleasant.
Shall I make some coffee?
A morning cup is the best.
Today is a perfect day for doing laundry.
Let's also wash the sheets!
Start the washing machine!
(Sound of the washing machine)
It's really nice to hang clothes outside.
I love the smell of the sun.
Now, what should I have for breakfast?
Today, I'll make French toast!
Mix eggs, milk, and sugar...
Soak the bread well and then fry it.
Pour syrup over it, and it's ready!
Let's eat!
Fluffy, sweet, and delicious!
Feeling happy from the morning.
After eating, let's do some tidying up...
Let's also clean the room.
Vacuum and wipe the surfaces.
Cleaning the windows makes me feel refreshed!
The room is sparkling clean.
Let's take a break now.
Let's play some music...
Shall I make some tea?
I'm thinking of having green tea today.
Pour hot water into the teapot and steep it carefully...
Take a sip and relax for a moment.
I love this quiet time.
What shall we do this afternoon?
I want to go for a walk.
Shall we walk to the park?
The breeze feels so nice.
I'm getting ready, see you later!
Take care!
(Sunlight filtering through the trees in the park)
There are few people, and it's quiet.
Shall we sit on the bench and read a book?
It's the continuation of the book I borrowed last time.
As I open the page, I am immediately immersed in the story.
This kind of reading is the best.
Sometimes the wind turns the pages.
I hate to finish reading it.
But I want to know what happens next!
To the next chapter... but then,
Huh? My stomach just growled.
Is it already that time?
Shall we head home soon?
On the way back, let's stop by the supermarket.
What should I make for dinner?
I want to eat hamburger steak today!
Then let's buy the ingredients.
Ground meat, onions, bread crumbs...
Don't forget the eggs and sauce.
The checkout was quick!
Well then, let's go home.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Let's start making the hamburger steak right away!
Sauté the onions and let them cool.
Mix with the ground meat and knead it well...
Shape it and fry it until it's sizzling!
It smells so good!
Make the sauce, pour it over...
It's done!
Let's eat!
Fluffy and juicy!
It goes well with rice.
So delicious and happy!
After eating, let's have some tea and chat a bit.
Today was a calm and fun day.
Looking forward to tomorrow again.
Good night.
Zzz...
(The silence of dawn)
Good morning.
Today is the weekend.
I'm thinking about what to do.
That's right, how about a picnic in the park after a long time?
Sounds good! Let's prepare a lunchbox.
Let's make rice balls with lots of ingredients!
What side dishes should we have?
Fried chicken and rolled omelette are the classics.
Yes, it brings back childhood memories.
Well then, let's start preparing!
Cook the rice and marinate the chicken.
Should the rolled omelette be on the sweet side?
Yes, with a gentle sweetness.
I've finished packing the lunchbox!
Don't forget the picnic mat.
Tea and juice are also ready.
The bag is light and easy to carry.
Now, let's head to the park!
(Sound of walking)
It's a beautiful day! The sky is so high.
Let's spread out the sheet in the shade of the trees.
Let's lay out the lunchboxes...
Let's eat!
Eating outside is exceptional.
I also brought some fried dumplings with wings.
Oh, they're crispy and delicious!
The breeze is so pleasant, I feel sleepy...
Shall we take a short nap after eating?
Nice, a peaceful time.
(Light snoring)
Feeling refreshed!
Shall we go for a walk soon?
Let's walk around the pond.
The ducks are swimming.
So cute... so relaxing.
Let's read a book on the bench for a while.
Weekend reading is a luxury.
The wind gently turns the pages.
It's already evening in the blink of an eye.
Shall we head home soon?
Would you like to have some ice cream before we go?
Which do you prefer, vanilla or matcha?
Today, I'll have the matcha!
It's slightly bitter, a mature flavor.
Let's chat on the way back.
Where should we go tomorrow?
How about a hot spring trip?
Sounds great, let's relax and unwind.
I'm looking forward to planning.
The weekend still continues.
We've arrived home!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
We had a lot of fun today.
Yes, it was a fulfilling day!
Shall we have a light dinner?
I think salad and soup will be good.
Alright, I'll prepare them.
Cut the vegetables...
I'll warm up the consommé soup.
It's refreshing and delicious!
Thank you for the meal.
For dessert, let's have some fruit.
Seasonal fruits are the best, aren't they?
Shall we watch a movie today?
Something funny would be nice.
Let's laugh and relax from the fatigue.
I'll play it now!
It's already making me laugh from the opening scene.
This actor's facial expressions are the best!
The timing of the gags is also great.
The dubbing adds a lot of flavor.
Haha, my abs hurt from laughing!
Laughing really boosts my energy.
I still have popcorn left.
Thanks! Perfect for watching a movie.
The climax has arrived!
As expected, the ending is just as good!
It made me laugh until the end.
The end credits also have a funny twist.
It was a great refreshment.
Now, let's finalize the plans for the hot spring trip.
I'll check the train schedule.
A departure at 9 a.m. seems just right.
Then leaving the house at 8 o'clock will give us plenty of time.
I want a traditional old-style inn.
This place has a wonderful open-air bath!
I've made the reservation, I'm looking forward to it!
Let's make a packing list.
Towels, change of clothes, camera...
A larger bag for souvenirs as well.
Do we need a late-night snack?
Let's buy onsen eggs at the site!
I probably won't be able to sleep because I'm so excited.
But we have to wake up early, right?
Let's start getting ready for bed soon.
Good night, tomorrow is the trip!
Zzz...
(Alarm sound)
Good morning, it's travel day!
Are you ready?
Yes, the suitcase is all set.
Let's have a quick breakfast.
A light meal with yogurt and fruit.
Energy recharge complete!
I'll call a taxi.
It should arrive soon.
Please take us to the station!
The morning city is sparkling.
We've arrived, thank you taxi!
I've already purchased the tickets online!
Checking the station bento at the platform!
The mountain vegetable rice bento looks delicious.
The train has arrived!
My reserved seat is by the window, lucky!
Departure!
The view from the train window is amazing.
The mountains are getting closer.
The greenery is dazzling.
Let's open the station bento!
The aroma is irresistible.
Let's savor it slowly.
After the tunnel, there's a riverbank.
I can see a cool babbling brook.
Are we arriving soon?
The next station is our destination!
Let's prepare to get off.
Arrived! The air is clear!
Let's head to the inn by bus.
Autumn leaves are spreading across the window!
It's like a painting.
We've arrived at the inn, with a lovely gate!
Welcome!
Please enjoy some welcome matcha.
It's relaxing, isn't it?
I'll show you to your room.
The scent of tatami mats is refreshing!
You can see the river from the window.
After unpacking, let's head straight to the foot bath!
It's warm and feels so good!
Relaxing while listening to the sound of the river.
The singing of small birds is also soothing.
We have some time before dinner.
Let's walk along the nearby trail.
A tunnel of autumn leaves continues.
I want to take lots of photos with my camera!
Click! (taking a photo)
Everywhere you look is a breathtaking view.
The sunset colors the mountains beautifully.
It's about time to head back.
The inn's noren (doorway curtain) warmly welcomes us.
Dinner starts at 6 PM.
I'm going to soak in the large bath.
Have a good soak!
The aroma of the cypress bath is wonderful!
It warms you to the core.
When you step outside to the open-air bath, you can see the starry sky!
The stars through the steam, it's a luxury.
I'm getting hungry.
Let's change into our yukata and head to dinner.
The menu looks luxurious!
The appetizer is seasonal hassun (small dishes).
It's a work of art in appearance.
Next is a sashimi boat!
It's fresh and sweet.
Let's also enjoy some local sake.
The aroma gently spreads.
The main dish is wagyu beef teppanyaki!
The sizzling sound whets my appetite.
It melts in my mouth...
This is what happiness feels like.
The finale is chestnut rice and red miso soup.
Enjoying the flavors of autumn!
The dessert is yuzu sherbet.
Refreshing and perfect!
Thank you for the meal.
Let's relax in the room.
With the sound of the river as background music...
I also bought hot spring eggs!
It's time for a late-night snack.
The runny yolk is the best.
Looking forward to tomorrow morning's bath.
I'm getting sleepy while watching the stars.
Good night, sweet dreams.
(The sound of the river continues)
The night quietly passes by...
...
(Birds singing in the morning)
Good morning, let's go to the open-air bath!
The morning sun is shining on the mountains.
The warm water and cold air feel so comfortable.
I saw a rainbow through the steam!
It's a lucky morning.
Breakfast is a Japanese and Western buffet.
Both grilled fish and croissants!
Don't forget the fresh juice.
Check-out is at 11 o'clock.
Until then, head to the souvenir corner.
The wooden chopsticks are cute!
I also bought some hot spring flower for my friend.
While talking about wanting to come again...
We're returning to the station by bus.
The return train is a leisurely local train.
Checking the travel photos on the train.
They all look like postcards!
Maybe I'll upload them to SNS.
Looking forward to the comments.
The rural scenery is flowing past the window.
The sadness of the trip coming to an end.
But I also miss home.
We've arrived, it's 'I'm home' time!
After all, home is the most comfortable〜
Unpacking can wait until later.
First, let's lay out the souvenirs.
The scent of hot spring steam comes back to me.
While soaking in the lingering memories of the trip…
There was one more hot spring egg left!
I'll brew some tea and enjoy it.
The melting yolk is, as expected, the best.
Shall I organize the photos?
Adding notes to the album.
Another volume of memories has been added.
Where should we go on our next trip?
The sea is nice, and snowy mountains are also good.
Planning the trip is also fun.
Shall we go to bed early tonight?
Good night. See you tomorrow.
The story continues—it's not over yet.