Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
The weather is nice today.
Yes, it's very good weather.
What will you do today?
From the afternoon
With friends
Watch a movie.
That sounds nice.
What movie is it?
It's an action movie.
Me too, action.
I like movies.
That's something to look forward to.
But first, let's have lunch.
Let's eat.
Yes, that's a good idea.
What would you like to eat?
I want to eat sushi.
That's nice.
I also like sushi.
Do you have any recommended shops?
Do you have it?
Yes,
That place is very
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Let's go there.
Let's go!
I hope the road isn't crowded.
Yes, I agree. I don't like traffic jams.
Shall we go by train?
Yes, that might be faster.
The station is this way.
I'll buy the tickets.
Thank you, I'll wait.
I've bought the tickets.
Thank you. Let's go.
The train will arrive in 5 minutes.
That's just right.
Oh, the train has arrived!
Let's get on.
There are empty seats.
Lucky us!
Where do we get off next?
It's the third station.
Got it.
What a beautiful view.
Indeed. Spring is beautiful.